那么应该重新命名什么呢？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Then
should be renamed what?
它应该被重命名为 this，store 函数以便以后运行。
It should be renamed this,
store function to run later.
没错。
Yeah, exactly.
将来的 data.store 我以后自动运行我的时候
Future data.store me to run
me later automatically when
从前面的获取调用中产生的后台任务完成并
the background task that came out of
the fetch call previously completes and
数值可能会更新。
the value probably gets updated.
虽然不够吸引人，但确实很准确。
Not catchy but it is accurate.
所以，我还要再加一个好处。
So, I will add one more benefit though.
所以，人们认为更干净，可读的风格，我会说，像 pseudo synchronous,
So, people think kind of cleaner, readable
style, I'll say, like pseudo synchronous,
看起来你运行得很好，但实际上不是。
it sort of looks like you're running
it right then but you really are not.
你传入的函数会像以前一样自动运行，不是你传入的，而是
You're passing in a function that's gonna
be auto run as before, not by you, but
作者: JavaScript。
by JavaScript.
它接受的是一个你没有放进去的输入，是 java 放进去的。
And it's taking an input that you didn't
put in there, java who put in there.
从背景来看，那个高音符号是自动的
From the background work,
that high string that's gonna be auto
自动运行时插入显示功能。
inserted into display
function when it's auto run.
我很喜欢。顺便说一下，一旦你看到 JavaScript
I love it.
By the way, once you see that JavaScript
或者一旦你看到 JavaScript 正在使用这个函数代码来显示，并且
or once one sees that JavaScript is
taking that function code of display, and
它会自动为你输入指纹。
it's running it for you by putting
print on it for you automatically.
它将输入插入到
And it's inserting the input for
你自然而然地，在这个意义上，这是非常慷慨的语言。
you automatically,
it's very generous language in that sense.
这种设计有一个很大的好处，那就是错误处理过程。
There is one big benefit to this design,
and it's that error handling process.
所以这真的很棒。
So this is really nice.
结果是人们，在这个承诺对象上，实际上还有另一个数组
It turns out people, there's actually
another array on this promise object
在幕后，另一个隐藏属性，它被称为拒绝。
behind the scenes, another hidden
property and it's called On Rejection.
它也是一个数组，我们可以把函数放进去。
And it's also an array into
which we can put functions.
当你与外部世界，尤其是网络上的东西互动时,
When you interact with the outside
world especially network stuff,
你总是会犯错。
you get errors all the time.
你不想运行你的显示功能，所以 Twitter 上的用户得到了一个可爱的
You don't wanna run your display function
so the user on Twitter gets a lovely
广播了错误的全部细节。
broadcast of the full
details of the error.
理想情况下，我们应该有一个单独的函数来处理这个错误。
Ideally we would have a separate function
is gonna run that handles that error.
也许它以某种方式为你记录了它，但是
Maybe it logs it for you in some way, but
可能只是给用户一个更好的体验。
probably just gives the user
a better experience.
它正在做类似的事情，也许，不管它是什么。
It's doing something similar,
maybe, whatever it might be.
现在，我们如何处理这个问题呢？
Now, how can we handle that?
好吧，你知道吗，我保证我会给我们这个惊人的功能。
Well, you know what, the promise I'll
just give us this amazing feature.
这意味着如果我们得到的是一个错误，而不是我们想要的实际响应对象,
That means if we get an error back not
the actual response object that we want,
任何错误，它都不会运行显示功能。
any error,
it's not gonna run that display function.
它甚至不会自动触发任何功能和未完成。
It's not even gonna auto trigger any
of the functions and unfulfilled.
它会触发任何你存储在拒绝中的功能。
It's going to trigger any functions
that you stored in on rejection.
我们如何在那里得到函数？
How do we get functions in there?
有两种方法一种是写未来数据有人知道吗？
Well, there's two ways, one would
be to write futureData.anyone know?
演讲者2: . 接住。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: .catch.
威尔 · 森塔斯:。 接着，完全正确，凯拉说得对。 抓住。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: .catch, spot on,
exactly, Kayla's right, .catch.
我们在这里传递的任何函数，都会进入你们的拒绝数组。
And any function we pass in there
is going in your rejection array.
另一种方法是作为第二个参数传递给 then,
The other way is to pass to
then as the second argument,
无论你想要什么功能，它都会在这里自动运行。
whatever function you want that's
gonna go in here to auto run on error.
第一个参数，将该函数设置为未实现。
First argument,
stick that function in unfulfilled.
然后我们接受第二个参数，第二个输入和
Then we'll take the second argument,
the second input and
把这个功能植入你的排斥系统。
stick that function in your rejected.
真是太好了,
That's really nice,
毫无疑问，这是一个非常好的错误处理方法。
that's a really really nice error
handling approach without a doubt.
好了，伙计们，我们有了，我们现在有了规则
All right folks, so there we have it,
we now have rules for
我们异步延迟代码的执行承诺延迟函数。
the execution of our asynchronously delay
code hold promise deferred functions.
这就是丹所说的承诺延迟作用,
This is what Dan was saying
promise deferred functions,
那些承诺延迟他们逃跑的人
ones that were attached to
a promise to delay them running
直到背景里发生了什么事。
until something happened
in the background.
将它们存储在微任务队列和传递的回调函数中
Store them in the micro task queue and
callback functions ones that were passed
类似计时器这样的外观函数,
in to one of these facade
functions like timer, sorry,
设置超时，让他们进入回调队列。
set timeout,
have them go in the callback queue.
当 web 浏览器功能，也就是 API 完成后,
When the web browser feature,
otherwise known as API finishes,
将函数添加到调用堆栈中，换句话说，运行它。
add the function to the call stack,
in other words, run it.
当调用堆栈为空且所有全局代码运行完毕时,
When call stack is empty and
all global code is finished running,
让事件循环为我们检查这个条件。
have the event loop check
this condition for us.
在我们知道代码是我会运行下一步,
Before we know it code
is I would run next,
将微任务队列中的函数优先于回调队列中的函数。
prioritize functions in the micro
task queue over the callback queue.
承诺网页浏览器的特性，回调和微任务队列以及
Promises web browser features,
the callback and micro task queues and
事件循环使我们能够构建非阻塞应用程序。
the event loop enable us to
build non blocking applications.
我们不必在这个 JavaScript 线程中等待。
We don't have to wait in this
single JavaScript thread.
我们必须在这里等待我们的数据回来。
We'd have to wait here for
our data to come back.
没有等待这条线，取我们不坐在这条线等待
No waiting on this line, fetch we're
not sitting on this line waiting for
数据回来。
the data to come back.
不不不。
No, no, no, no.
我的意思是，不是我们做的普通代码,
I mean, no in regular code we do,
在函数代码中，你要一直站在那条线上直到你完成它。
in function code, you're staying
on that line til you finished it.
但它不是一个常规的函数调用。
But it's not a regular function call.
这是一个用于设置后台工作的 facade 函数。
It's a facade function for
setting up background work.
不管要花多长时间,
However long it takes,
我们不能预测我们的浏览器功能什么时候会在后台完成。
we can't predict when our Browser features
work will finish in the background.
我们不知道它什么时候结束。
We can't know exactly
when it's gonna finish.
所以我们不能让一行代码运行后台数据
So we can't kinda have the line of code
that's gonna use that background data run
现在。
right now.
因为我们告诉它什么时候该跑,
Because we tell it when to run,
我们必须依靠 JavaScript 来知道后台工作何时完成,
we got to rely on JavaScript that knows
when the background work is done,
自动触发函数在那个时刻运行。
to automatically trigger
the function to run on that moment.
这就是为什么我们人们可以建立这些非阻塞的动态,
This is what allows us people to
build these non blocking dynamic,
快速应用。
fast applications.
我们可以在后台设置大量的东西
We can handle setting up a ton
of stuff in the background
当我们在前台比赛，运行我们的代码，响应,
while we race on in the foreground,
running our code, being responsive,
响应用户交互，构建这些动态应用程序。
responsive to users interactions,
building these dynamic applications.
这就是让 JavaScript 变得非常非常特别，非常好用的原因。
This is what really makes JavaScript
very very special and very usable.